[
    {
        "question": "Which Protocol do Internet Browsers (Chrome, Firefox, Internet Explorer) use?",
        "options": [
            "SMTP",
            "FTP",
            "AOL",
            "HTTPS"
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Layer 6 of OSI model?",
        "options": [
            "Physical",
            "Presentation",
            "Network",
            "Transport"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Within the Session Layer, what connection allows applications to talk through ports?",
        "options": [
            "Ports",
            "Ethernet",
            "Sockets",
            "IPP"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "When a sender wants to know the physical address of a device it broadcasts what?",
        "options": [
            "ARP Request",
            "Checksum",
            "Broadcast Request",
            "ARP Reply"
        ],
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "What is an Internet Control Message Protocol to check if a destistination device is responding?",
        "options": [
            "UDP Reply",
            "ICMP Test",
            "ICMP Reply",
            "ICMP Ping"
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "In 2020 nearly all websites use what type of cryptographic protocol?",
        "options": [
            "Transport Layer Security",
            "Secure Socket Layer",
            "Transfer Layer Security",
            "Secure Layer Security,"
        ],
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "What OSI layer does Chrome and other browsers use TLS to encrypt data?",
        "options": [
            "Application",
            "Network",
            "Session",
            "Presentation"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which network protocol is often used for video game streaming in which some packet drop is preferable to overall latency?",
        "options": [
            "Connectionless Protocol",
            "User Datagram Protocol",
            "Transmission Control Protocol",
            "File Transfer Protocol"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which network protocol type can establish a secure connection before sending data?",
        "options": [
            "Connectionless Protocol",
            "User Datagram Protocol",
            "Transmission Control Protocol",
            "File Transfer Protocol"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of small pieces of information sent via TCP/IP?",
        "options": [
            "Packets",
            "Capsules",
            "Data points",
            "Files"
        ],
        "answer": 0
    }
]